<resources>
    <string name="app_name">bagU</string>
    <string name="coffee_shops">Coffee shops</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="shopping_centers">Shopping centers</string>
    <string name="name">Name: %s</string>
    <string name="address">Address: %s</string>
    <string name="mobile_number">Mobile #: %s</string>

    <string name="cafe_de_angelo">Cafe de Angelo</string>
    <string name="cafe_de_angelo_info">
        Cafe de Angelo is a quaint coffee shop tucked in a dainty garden along. This garden
        cafe is a popular spot for locals and tourists to hang out and spend a chill afternoon.
        Take your pick from their house blends—De Angelo Blend, Barako, and Italian Roast—to go
        with your choice of comfort food like their Zoolander Burger and Chicharon Pasta for
        your midday fill.
    </string>
    <string name="cafe_de_angelo_address">54 Chapis Village, Marcos Highway, Baguio City</string>
    <string name="cafe_de_angelo_contact_number">0915 345 4855 or 0905 487 9711</string>

    <string name="cafe_by_the_ruins">Cafe by the Ruins</string>
    <string name="cafe_by_the_ruins_info">
        Cafe by the Ruins was rebuilt into a romantic, modern cafe, reclaiming its title as
        one of the. A visit to this iconic cafe is not complete without trying their signature
        Ruins Coffee infused with cinnamon and cardamom that\'s sure to uplift your mood.
        Plus, you can take home-baked pastries like Luisa\'s Ensaymada and Ernie\'s
        Camote Bread that are sure to be a hit with the family!
    </string>
    <string name="cafe_by_the_ruins_address">25 Shuntug Rd, Baguio City</string>
    <string name="cafe_by_the_ruins_contact_number">(074) 442 4010</string>

    <string name="cafe_yagam">Cafe Yagam</string>
    <string name="cafe_yagam_info">
        Taste the best Arabica coffee in the Philippines at Cafe Yagam, one of the most beloved
        cafes in Baguio. This well-loved coffee shop permanently closed its store last September
        due to the pandemic but opened a new stall called Nest Coffee Roasters two months
        later—much to the delight of its loyal patrons. This new stall located in Calle Uno
        serves coffee and pastries to those who missed and want to taste. The cafe\ns new small
        and humble red-bricked stall allows the coffee to take center stage. If you happen to
        be in Baguio, don\nt forget to drop by, grab a cup of coffee, and take a bag of Yagam
        Coffee home!
    </string>
    <string name="cafe_yagam_address">
        Calle Uno Building, #3 Escoda (First Road) cor. Naguilian Road, Quezon Hill, Baguio City
    </string>

    <string name="ihawjuan">IhawJuan</string>
    <string name="ihawjuan_info">
        If you like grilled food, then you would love to know that there\'s a place in Baguio
        where not only can you get unlimited, but you also get to grill the food yourself!
        For P199 for lunch and P249 for dinner, you can get to grill food all you want at
        IhawJuan. There is a wide selection of meat, vegetables, seafood, and grilling and
        dipping sauces at the counter. Fried rice, plain rice, and soup are unlimited too.
    </string>
    <string name="ihawjuan_address">
        Ground Floor, Blue Mountain Hotel, 18 Marcos
        Highway, Baguio City
    </string>
    <string name="ihawjuan_contact_number">09774035575</string>

    <string name="te_quiero_tapas_bar">Te Quiero Tapas Bar</string>
    <string name="te_quiero_tapas_bar_info">
        Te Quiero Tapas Bar offers unlimited tapa for P350 every Friday.
        Enjoy free live acoustic music during Tapas Nights.
    </string>
    <string name="te_quiero_tapas_bar_address">
        Microtel Inns and Suites, Upper Session Road, Baguio City
    </string>
    <string name="te_quiero_tapas_bar_contact_number">(074) 619 3333</string>

    <string name="omai_khan">O\'Mai Khan</string>
    <string name="omai_khan_info">
        Have your own platter of Mongolian Barbeque for P210. If you plan to eat in groups,
        try O\'Mai Khan\'s Mongolian Hot Pot, which is P420, good for 4 people.
    </string>
    <string name="omai_khan_address"> Upper Session Road, Baguio City</string>
    <string name="omai_khan_contact_number">(074) 442 5885</string>

    <string name="burnham_park">Burnham Park</string>
    <string name="burnham_park_info">
        Burnham Park is a large city park located in front of The Melvin Jones Grandstand,
        in Baguio City, Philippines. There are many activities to be enjoyed by visitors,
        such as boating on the man-made lake, skateboarding and riding rides on the amusement
        park\'s kiddie rides, eating strawberry taho and other local delicacies at food stalls,
        or picnicking under the pine trees.
    </string>
    <string name="burnham_park_address">Jos Abad Santos Drive, Baguio City</string>

    <string name="wright_park">Wright Park</string>
    <string name="wright_park_info">Located in the heart of Baguio City, The Wright Park is a
        tranquil natural area that is perfect for nature lovers and those who want to get some
        exercise. There are several walking trails and horseback riding opportunities available,
        making it an ideal place to spend a day out.
    </string>
    <string name="wright_park_address">The Mansion, Romulo Drive, Baguio City</string>

    <string name="baguio_botanical_garden">Baguio Botanical Garden</string>
    <string name="baguio_botanical_garden_info">
        The Baguio Botanical Garden is a beautiful spot in the city where visitors can explore
        a variety of plants and flowers. The park has a variety of different areas, including
        individual pavilions dedicated to the cities that Baguio shares relationships with.
        There are also plenty of benches to relax on and activities to do, like taking a lunch
        break or exploring the gardens. If you\'re interested in nature then this is definitely
        a place you should visit.
    </string>
    <string name="baguio_botanical_garden_address">37 Leonard Wood Rd, Baguio City</string>

    <string name="atonement_cathedral">
        Our Lady of the Atonement Cathedral (Diocese of Baguio)
    </string>
    <string name="atonement_cathedral_info">
        The catholic cathedral in Baguio City, Philippines is a stunning building with
        distinctive pink façade and rose window. It is popular for its beauty and is one
        of the top tourist destinations in Baguio City.
    </string>
    <string name="atonement_cathedral_address">
        2600 Steps To Our Lady Of Atonement Cathedral, Baguio City
    </string>

    <string name="bell_church">Bell Church</string>
    <string name="bell_church_info">
        The Bell Church is a Buddhist temple located in the town of La Trinidad, halfway
        between Baguio City and the city of La Trinidad, in the Philippines. The
        temple features Taoist architecture alongside some Buddhist features, and is
        a popular tourist destination due to its tranquil environment and views from
        the courtyard. A small lily pond is included.
    </string>
    <string name="bell_church_address">
        Bell Church Rd, La Trinidad, Benguet
    </string>

    <string name="sm_city_baguio">SM City Baguio</string>
    <string name="sm_city_baguio_info">
        Baguio isn\'t immune to the infectious shopping bug that SM Super-malls brings to the
        country’s major cities with the existence of SM City Baguio.

        \n\nLocated in Luneta Hill in Upper Session Road, SM City Baguio opened in 2003 and since
        then has been the largest shopping mall in the whole North Luzon region. It is also
        the only mall to not utilize a central air-conditioning system and the second mall
        to make use of natural lighting, the other being the SM Mall of Asia.

        \n\nIt has all the makings of your usual SM mall: a food court filled with different fusion
        cuisines; an activity area where they host lively local events; a department store;
        as well as multiple levels dedicated to beauty and well-being, appliance and home needs,
        and gadget and tech retails. What sets it apart, though, is the stunning view from
        each level\'s balconies where you can see Burnham Park, Baguio Cathedral, and even
        Session Road. It is also home to the only DFA passport office in the Cordillera region.
    </string>
    <string name="sm_city_baguio_address">
        Luneta Hill, Upper Session Road, Baguio City
    </string>

    <string name="porta_vaga_mall">Porta Vaga Mall</string>
    <string name="porta_vaga_mall_info">
        Session Road in Baguio is considered as the city\'s cauldron of business and trade,
        where merchants big and small open shop to the teeming tourists and shoppers.
        Due to shopping centers like the famous Porta Vaga Mall, which opened in 2002,
        business in Session Road is always alive.
    </string>
    <string name="porta_vaga_mall_address">Porta Vaga, Session Road, Baguio City</string>

    <string name="tiong_san_harrison">Tiong San Harrison</string>
    <string name="tiong_san_harrison_info">
        Some businesses in Baguio have existed long enough that they have been a pillar of
        what has been deemed the \"Baguio City Experience.\" Such a pillar is Tiong San,
        who dubs itself \"Suki ng Bayan\" (the people\'s favorite).

        \n\nAnd why shouldn\'t it? Tiong San has been operating for over seven decades among
        three generations of proprietors, building a sense of trust and value for shoppers
        in the region along the way.

        \n\nCurrently, Tiong San shopping center caters to a vast array of local and global brands,
        from apparel to houseware to tech peripherals. They also have their own full-range
        supermarkets and meat shops. Tiong San has also partnered with government agencies
        and local government units to promote local industry, environmental sustainability,
        and entrepreneurship.
    </string>
    <string name="tiong_san_harrison_address">Harrison Road, Baguio City</string>
</resources>